they raised 200 million
US dollars at a
1 4 billion dollar
valuation and this is
get Indonesian farming company
Fish farmers like get
IOT to just automatically
feed the and help
those fish farms then
sell the fish get
cheaper feed on demand
24 hour support It's
like a farmers cooperative
Yeah you're that way
last year they did
372 million US dollars
in revenue and this
year they're closing out
700 million US dollars
and past five years
including this year all
profitable completely profitable company
right so Agriculture there
is a lot of
money in it and
it's so under penetrated
by technology So many
countries not just Indonesia
Malaysia and elsewhere It's
like the per for
any crop or any
yield any livestock or
whatever the productivity is
much less than other
countries so the extent
that we can find
financial like any kind
of like Fintech tech
means or kind of
IOT kind of means
to increase the productivity
It's fantastic